華納兄弟影片公司
時代華納公司
艾肯娛樂公司
索尼影業
哥倫比亞     影業公司
索尼旗下公司
複製人
是泰瑞公司研製的合成人，被用於外星殖民地,它們力量過人，是理想的勞動力
因為一系列暴亂，複製人的生產遭禁，泰瑞公司破產
21世紀20年代中葉，生態系統崩潰，企業家尼安德·華萊士由此發跡，他的人造農業專利避免了饑荒發生
華萊士取得泰瑞爾公司的殘餘部分，並創造出新的複製人產品線，他們服從命令
許多壽命無限的舊型號複製人連鎖8型倖存下來，他們受到追捕及“除役”
那些追捕他們的獵手得名：
銀翼殺手
加利福尼亞 2049年
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
KD6-3.7
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
自動駕駛模式
偵探
KD6-3.7
狀態
有效
洛杉磯警局
希望你不介意我擅自進來了
I hope you don't mind me taking the liberty.
我很小心  沒帶進來灰塵
I was careful not to drag in any dirt.
我不介意灰塵
I don't mind the dirt.
但我很介意
I do mind...
不速之客
unannounced visits.
你是員警嗎
You police?
你是薩珀·莫爾頓嗎  公民號NK68514
Are you Sapper Morton? Civic number NK68514?
-我是個農民  -我看出來了
- I'm a farmer. - I saw that.
你種什麼
What do you farm?
這是個蛋白質農場
It's a protein farm.
由華萊士設計
Wallace design.
我聞到的是這個嗎
Is that what I smell?
是我種的留著自己吃的東西
Grow that just for me.
大蒜
Garlic.
你可以嘗嘗
Go on, try some.
不用了  謝謝你
No, thank you.
我比較喜歡空著肚子
I prefer to keep an empty stomach
去處理一天裡難熬的部分
until the hard part of the day is done.
你來這兒多久了
How long you been here?
從2020年開始
Since 2020.
你並非一直都是個農民  是嗎
But you haven't always been a farmer, have you?
你的包
Your bag.
那是殖民地醫療用包
It's colonial medical use.
由軍隊發放
Military issue.
你以前駐在哪  卡蘭星嗎
Where were you? Calantha?
那場景想必很兇殘
Must have been brutal.
你是想逮捕我嗎
Plan on taking me in?
讓他們把我解剖了看看
Let them take a look inside?
莫爾頓先生
Mr. Morton...
如果能逮捕你
if taking you in is an option...
那我很是樂意
I would much prefer that to the alternative.
你肯定知道早晚會有人找上門的
I'm sure you knew it would be someone in time.
很遺憾  那個人是我
I'm sorry it had to be me.
都一樣
Good as any.
如果你不介意
Now, if you don't mind...
能否請你往左上看
if you could just look up and to the left, please.
請不要站起來
Please don't get up.
殺死你的同類是什麼感受
How's it feel killing your own kind?
我不用"退休"同類  因為我們不會逃
I don't retire my own kind because we don't run.
只有舊型號才逃
Only older models do.
你們這些新型號樂意幹這種髒活
And you new models are happy scraping the shit...
是因為你們從未見過奇跡
because you've never seen a miracle.
全部拍照取證
Just photograph everything.
呼叫長官
Madam, please.
洛杉磯警局來電
Incoming L.A.P.D. Re-codec hash.
洛杉磯警局
你受傷了  我可不付你醫療費
You're hurt. I'm not paying for that.
-我粘一下就好  -彙報
- I'll glue it. - And?
殘存的幾個連鎖8型之一
One of the tail-end Nexus 8s.
他好像對你下手不輕
He looks like he could take your head off.
是啊
He tried.
他去了卡蘭星之後擅自離隊
He went AWOL after Calantha...
同行的還有幾個  也要處理掉
with a few more in his outfit I wouldn't mind closing out.
-就他一個人嗎  -就他一個人
- Just him? - Just him.
回來測基線
Come on home for your baseline.
稍等  長官
One moment, madam.
地下30米最大深度掃描
Thirty meters to maximum depth.
洛杉磯警局證物
那是什麼
What is that?
我派個挖掘小隊過去
I'll send a dig team.
風暴前回來
Come on home before the storm.
洛杉磯警局
KD6-3.7警官
Officer KD6 - 3.7.
-開始吧  準備好了嗎  -好了  長官
- Let's begin. Ready? - Yes, sir.
背誦你的基線
Recite your baseline.
血黑色的虛無開始編織
And blood-black nothingness began to spin.
一個網路  細胞之間相連
A system of cells interlinked within cells...
再相連  與那主幹再相連
interlinked within cells interlinked within one stem.
滾開  劣種
Fuck off, skin-job.
於是在那黑暗襯托下
And dreadfully distinct against the dark,
顯現一座噴泉向上高噴的白水柱
a tall white fountain played.
-細胞  -細胞
- Cells. - Cells.
-你去過孤兒院嗎  細胞  -細胞
- Have you ever been in an institution? Cells. - Cells.
創傷後基線測試
警官  KD6-3.7
2049年6月30日
-他們把你關在監獄裡嗎  細胞  -細胞
- Do they keep you in a cell? Cells. - Cells.
如果你沒有盡責
When you're not performing your duties,
-他們會把你關進小房間嗎  細胞  -細胞
- do they keep you in a little box? - Cells.
-相連  -相連
- Interlinked. - Interlinked.
牽著你所愛之人的手是什麼感覺  相連
What's it like to hold the hand of someone you love? Interlinked.
相連
Interlinked.
他們有教過你指尖相對的感覺嗎  相連
Did they teach you how to feel finger to finger? Interlinked.
相連
Interlinked.
你渴望你的心與人相連嗎  相連
Do you long for having your heart interlinked? Interlinked.
相連
Interlinked.
-你夢想過與誰相連嗎  -相連
- Do you dream about being interlinked? - Interlinked.
懷抱你的孩子是什麼感受  相連
What's it like to hold your child in your arms? Interlinked.
相連
Interlinked.
你是否覺得自己有一部分缺少了
Do you feel that there's a part of you that's missing?
-相連  -相連
- Interlinked. - Interlinked.
-細胞之間相連  -細胞之間相連
- Within cells interlinked. - Within cells interlinked.
說三遍
Why don't you say that three times?
細胞之間相連  細胞之間相連
Within cells interlinked. Within cells interlinked.
細胞之間相連
Within cells interlinked.
好了
We're done.
很穩定  K
Constant K.
你可以去領獎金了
You can pick up your bonus.
謝謝你  長官
Thank you, sir.
注意  不要靠近
Caution, keep clear.
隨時隨地聯繫外星殖民地
Connect to Off-world any time, any place.
20分鐘後開始
Packages start at 20 minutes.
提供多種選擇
Many options available.
喬伊會去任何你想讓她去的地方
Joi goes anywhere you want her to go.
隨時隨地聯繫外星殖民地
Connect to Off-world any time, any place.
20分鐘後開始
Packages start at 20 minutes.
帥氣的鐵皮兵你怎麼了？
你現在回家了啊，爛人？
誰他媽的在這兒等你？
我要踢掉你的腿，雜種！
（這種語言是未來洛杉磯的混合語言：Cityspeak）
滾蛋 皮子貨
K  我沒聽見你  你回來早了
K? I didn't hear you. You're early.
你不想讓我回家嗎
You want me to come back?
-快去洗洗吧  -遵命  夫人
- Just go scrub. - Yes, ma'am.
你的會開得怎樣
How was your meeting?
就平時那樣
The usual.
你今天過得如何
How was your day?
我都快得幽閉恐懼症了
I'm getting cabin fever.
99.9%消毒水
99.9 percent detoxified water.
工作時出了點意外
I had an accident at work.
襯衣大概是毀了
I think I ruined my shirt.
我確信我能補好它  拿給我看看
I'm sure I can fix that for you. Let me take a look at it.
我得喝一杯
I need a drink.
-你想先喝一杯嗎  -給我倒一杯吧
- Do you want a drink first? - Pour me one, will you?
我在嘗試新菜譜
I'm trying a new recipe.
再多練練就能成了
I just need a bit more practice.
別忙活了
Don't fuss.
我應該醃久一點的  希望不會幹
I should have marinated it longer. I hope it isn't dry.
你知道這首歌是1966年由重顯唱片公司發行的嗎
Did you know this song was released in 1966 on Reprise Records?
當時是榜單上第一名
It was number one on the charts.
很快就好了  最後再收個尾
It won't be much longer. Just putting on the finishing touches.
好啦  準備好了  希望你喜歡
Okay, it's ready. I hope you're gonna like it.
我說了不用忙活的
I told you not to fuss.
但我仍然...
And yet....
好啦  用餐愉快
Voilà! Bon appétit.
我想你了  寶貝甜心
I missed you, baby sweet.
親愛的  這太美了
Honey, it's beautiful.
把腿翹起來
Just put your feet up.
放輕鬆
Relax.
今天可夠嗆了吧
Was a day?
是很夠嗆
It was a day.
你讀給我聽好嗎
Would you read to me?
弗拉基米爾·納博科夫
《微暗的火》
能讓你好受一些
It'll make you feel better.
-你討厭那本書  -我也不想讀
- You hate that book. - I don't wanna read either.
我們跳舞吧
Let's dance.
你想跳舞  還是想拆禮物
Do you wanna dance, or do you wanna open your present?
什麼禮物
What present?
-這個  -今天是什麼日子
- This one. - What's the occasion?
就當做是...
Let's just say...
-我們的紀念日吧  -是嗎
- it's our anniversary. - Is it?
不是  但我們就當做是吧
No, but let's just say that it is.
好嗎
Okay?
紀念日快樂
Happy anniversary.
投射儀
An emanator.
嬌伊
身高：168cm
身材：苗條
臉部：經典
皮膚：橄欖色
眼睛：棕色
唇色：非彩
發色：深色
髮型：劉海
人種：古巴
語言：英語
檢測到投射儀  正在連接
華萊士
謝謝
Thank you.
親愛的  現在你想去哪裡都可以了
Honey, you can go anywhere you want in the world now.
你想先去哪
Where do you wanna go first?
和你在一起時我很開心
I'm so happy when I'm with you.
你不必這麼說
You don't have to say that.
嬌伊系統自動停止 / 雇主來電
語音訊息
發送至警官 KD6-3.7
嬌伊系統自動停止 / 雇主來電
語音訊息
發送至警官 KD6-3.7
嬌伊系統自動停止 / 雇主來電
語音訊息
發送至警官 KD6-3.7
播  放
喬什警司
洛城警局除役部門
嬌伊系統自動停止 / 雇主來電
語音訊息
發送至警官 KD6-3.7
播  放
喬什警司
洛城警局除役部門
挖掘完成了  我們發現了一個新線索
The dig's come through. We have a new lead.
馬上過來
Get down here.
嬌伊系統自動停止 / 雇主來電
語音訊息
發送至警官 KD6-3.7
通話結束
喬什警司
洛城警局除役部門
碳讀數  14.6GPH
Carbon read: 14.6 GPH.
這箱子是個士兵個人用品箱
Your box is a military footlocker,
屬於薩珀·莫爾頓
issued to Sapper Morton...
被當成了棺材  有創意
creatively repurposed as an ossuary:
裡面裝了一箱屍骨
a box of bones.
除了骨頭  就只有頭髮
Nothing else in it but hair.
土壤樣本檢測顯示她已經入土30年了
The soil samples indicate that she's been buried for 30 years.
骨頭全部被拆開洗乾淨
Bones all dismantled, fully cleaned,
然後仔細安放好了
meticulously laid to rest.
"她"
"She"?
死因是什麼  珂珂
Cause of death, Coco?
沒有裂痕  沒有外傷的跡象  但是...
No breaks, no sign of trauma, except...
髂骨骨折了
a fracture through the ilium.
產道狹窄  胎兒一定是被卡住了
It's a narrow birth canal. Baby must have got stuck.
她當時懷孕了嗎
She was pregnant?
所以他沒殺她
So he didn't kill her?
她死於難產
She died in childbirth.
那是什麼
What's that?
往回
Go back.
放大
Closer.
再放大
那是什麼
What's that?
骼脊上的切口
Notching in the iliac crest.
尖端很細  像是把手術刀
It's fine-point, like a scalpel.
看著像是緊急剖腹產
That looks like an emergency C-section.
切口很規則  沒有掙扎的痕跡
The cuts are clean. No sign of a struggle.
他曾經是軍醫
He was a combat medic.
也許他想救她  但沒成功
Maybe he tried to save her, and he just couldn't.
他看著可不像是會救人的那種
He didn't seem like the saving type.
他不辭勞苦埋了她
He went to the trouble of burying her.
一個多愁善感的劣種
A sentimental skin-job.
抱歉
Sorry.
那孩子在哪
So where's the kid?
你掃描了整片區域嗎
You scan the whole field?
只有泥土和蟲子  沒有其他屍體了
Just dirt and worms. No other bodies.
也許被他吃了
Maybe he ate it.
不可能
That's not possible.
她是個複製人
She was a Replicant.
懷孕了的
Pregnant.
這個世界  界限分明
The world is built on a wall.
把人和複製人區分開
It separates kind.
不管哪一邊知道這個界限消失了
Tell either side there's no wall,
都會引發戰爭
you bought a war.
或是屠殺
Or a slaughter.
所以你剛剛...
So what you saw...
什麼都沒有看見
didn't happen.
遵命  長官
Yes, madam.
我的職責就是維護秩序
It is my job to keep order.
這就是我們的職責  我們維護秩序
That's what we do here. We keep order.
您想解決這件事嗎
You want it gone?
抹除一切
Erase everything.
-孩子也不放過嗎  -一切痕跡
- Even the child? - All trace.
你還有話要說嗎
You have anything more to say?
我從沒退休過自然出生的東西
I've never retired something that was born before.
有什麼區別
What's the difference?
自然出生意味著有靈魂  我猜
To be born is to have a soul, I guess.
你是在拒絕我嗎
Are you telling me no?
我都不知道有違抗命令這一說  長官
I wasn't aware that was an option, madam.
不錯
Attaboy.
你沒有那東西也挺好的
You've been getting on fine without one.
什麼東西  長官
What's that, madam?
靈魂
A soul.
你們這些新型號樂意幹髒活
And you new models are happy scraping the shit...
是因為你們從未見過奇跡
because you've never seen a miracle.
華萊士公司
地球總部
我來查一個以前的序號
Just checking in on an old serial number.
有DNA嗎
Confirmation DNA?
有頭髮
I got hair.
掃描物品
標本 45-27
第A5-869號抽屜
老型號
An old one.
大斷電之前的
Pre-Blackout.
那就有點難找了
That's gonna be tough.
大斷電後剩下的數據不多
Not much from then.
留下的也是...
And what's there is...
滄海一粟
thick milky.
您可以根據需要定制複製人
You can customize them as much as you'd like.
讓他們盡可能地與人類相似
As human as you want them to be.
不過您是想在鑽井現場使用  對吧
But your operation is strictly a drill site, isn't it?
是我就不會把錢浪費在
I wouldn't waste your money
提高智力  忠誠度和外表上
on intelligence, attachment or appeal.
還是說您想在訂單里加點情趣型號的
Unless you'd like to add some pleasure models to your order.
自動警告
背景資訊檢查請求
我們改天再聊  行嗎
Would it be possible to reschedule this call, please?
所有人都記得大斷電的時候自己在哪  你呢
Everyone remembers where they were at the Blackout. You?
那是我生產前的事了
That was a little before my time.
我當時和父母在家裡  度過了黑暗的十天
I was home with my folks, then 10 days of darkness.
所有機器都停止了運行
Every machine stopped cold.
等來電的時候  我們的資料都被抹去了
When the lights came back, we were wiped clean.
照片  檔  所有的資料都沒了
Photos, files, every bit of data, gone.
銀行記錄也沒了
Bank records too.
那倒無所謂
Didn't mind that.
只不過留存下來的居然是紙質記錄
It's funny it's only paper that lasted.
畢竟我們把所有東西都存在了硬碟裡
I mean, we had everything on drives.
什麼都放在裡面
Everything, everything, everything.
我媽現在一想到我的嬰兒照沒了都會哭呢
My mom still cries over the lost baby pictures.
那真可惜  你小時候一定很可愛
Well, it's a shame. You must have been adorable.
很零碎  沒多少資訊
Pretty fractured. Not much on it.
禁令頒佈前  生產的上一代複製人
One of the last gens, pre-Prohibition.
標準配置
Standard issue.
-泰瑞公司研發的  -其他資訊呢
- Made by Tyrell. - And?
不足為奇
Unremarkable.
"Unremarkable"?
我們肯定能給他找到其他線索
There must be something else we can find for him.
又找回了個舊複製人
Another prodigal serial number returns.
30年的案子終於結了
A 30-year-old open case finally closed.
謝謝您  警官
Thank you, officer.
華萊士先生派我來的  我叫露芙
I'm here for Mr. Wallace. I'm Luv.
他給你取了名字
He named you.
你一定很特別
Must be special.
我是代華萊士先生來的
I'm here for Mr. Wallace.
請跟我走
Follow me.
老一代複製人壞了整個項目的名聲
The ancient models give the entire endeavor a bad name.
這是華萊士先生給世界帶來的饋贈  不是嗎
What a gift, don't you think, from Mr. Wallace to the world?
要不是他收購了泰瑞公司
The outer colonies would never
讓這項技術死灰復燃
have flourished had he not bought Tyrell...
外星殖民地也不會這麼興旺
revivified the technology.
我們做出的貢獻遠不僅如此
To say the least of what we do.
你好像也是我們的顧客
I see you're also a customer.
對我們的產品還滿意嗎
Are you satisfied with our product?
她非常逼真  謝謝
She's very realistic. Thank you.
到了  所有的廢棄資訊都在這
Here. All the junk is in here.
你真走運  華萊士先生喜歡收藏資料
Lucky for you, Mr. Wallace is a data hoarder.
這裡好久沒人來過了
No one's been down here in ages.
請見諒
Sorry about that.
我們那時所有的記憶體資料
All our memory bearings from the time.
在大斷電時都受到了損害
They were all damaged in the Blackout.
不過有時會有片段倖存
But there are sometimes fragments.
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
泰瑞爾檔案
視頻資料
2019年11月20日
你有個兒子
You got a little boy.
他在向你展示他的蝴蝶標本  還有殺蟲罐
He shows you his butterfly collection, plus the killing jar.
我會帶他去看醫生
I'd take him to the doctor.
-有只黃蜂爬在你的手臂上  -我會殺了它
- There's a wasp crawling on your arm. - I'd kill it.
你在讀一本雜誌
You're reading a magazine.
其中有一頁是一位女性的全幅裸體照
You come across a full-page nude photo of a girl.
這是在測試
Is this testing
我是複製人還是同性戀  戴克先生
whether I'm a Replicant or a lesbian, Mr. Deckard?
請直接回答問題
Just answer the questions, please.
至少對某些人來說  還不知道她是誰
It was unclear what she was, at least to someone.
這是在做測試
This was a test.
我們當時也沒認出來
We were difficult to spot then.
你找到她的方式有什麼不尋常的嗎
Was there anything unusual about how you found her?
還開始了正式調查
To warrant an official investigation?
你也知道人們是怎麼看待舊複製人的
You know how people are about old serial numbers.
他們瞭解了這些複製人的下落後會更安心
Everyone just sleeps better when they know where they got to.
她喜歡他
She likes him.
喜歡誰
Who?
戴克警官
This Officer Deckard.
她想激怒他
She's trying to provoke him.
被問及私人問題的時候會讓人亢奮
It is invigorating being asked personal questions.
會讓人覺得
Makes one feel...
被需要
desired.
你喜歡你的工作嗎  警官
Do you enjoy your work, officer?
感謝華萊士先生讓你來接待
Please thank Mr. Wallace for your time.
你曾與戴克警官共事
You worked with Officer Deckard...
過去的時候
back in the day.
能和我說說他嗎
What can you tell me about him?
他喜歡單獨行動
He liked to work alone.
我也是
So did I.
所以我們就做了搭檔  好各自行動
So we worked together to keep it that way.
就這些
That was it.
還有其他資訊嗎
Anything else you can tell me?
他對這個世界沒有眷念
He wasn't long for this world.
為什麼
How so?
他的眼神
Something in his eyes.
我能怎樣聯繫到他
Any idea how I could contact him?
聯繫不到
None.
他退休了
He's nyugdíjas.
退役了
Retired.
怎麼回事
What happened?
大概得到他想要的了
Probably got what he wanted.
得以孤身一人
To be alone.
歡迎回來  先生
Welcome back, sir.
你想在裝運前審查一下新型號嗎  先生
You wanted to review the new model, sir, before shipment?
天使永遠不該不拿禮物
An angel should never enter the kingdom of heaven...
就進入天堂
without a gift.
你能至少說出"嬰孩降生"嗎
Can you at least pronounce, "a child is born"?
新型號
A new model.
那我們來看看她吧
Well, let us see her, then.
第一反應
The first thought...
人們會感到恐懼
one tends to fear...
來保護自己的肉體
to preserve the clay.
真是迷人
It's fascinating.
在我們還未搞清楚自己是什麼之前
Before we even know what we are...
我們就害怕失去了
we fear to lose it.
生日快樂
Happy birthday.
現在我們來看看你
Now, let's have a look at you.
我們製造天使
We make angels...
來造福文明社會
in the service of civilization.
是的  過去有過壞天使
Yes, there were bad angels once.
我現在造的是好天使
I make good angels now.
由此我們征服了九個新世界
That is how I took us to nine new worlds.
九個
Nine.
孩子數手指頭也能數到九
A child can count to nine on fingers.
那些星球應該屬於我們
We should own the stars.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
文明的每次飛躍都是以可支配的[一次性的]勞動力為基礎的
Every leap of civilization was built off the back of a disposable workforce.
我們不再對奴隸感興趣
We lost our stomach for slaves...
除非是改造過的
unless engineered.
但我只能造出這麼多
But I can only make so many.
那貧瘠的牧場
That barren pasture...
寸草不生
empty...
因鹽鹼而荒蕪
and salted...
就這裡
right here.
星際間的死區
The dead space between the stars.
這裡  我們必須為天堂而改變這裡
And this, the seat that we must change for heaven.
我無法讓他們生育  我發誓我努力過了
I cannot breed them. So help me, I have tried.
我們需要比以往更多的複製人
We need more Replicants than can ever be assembled.
數百萬  由此來製造數萬億
Millions, so we can be trillions more.
我們可以攻佔伊甸園  並將她奪回
We could storm Eden and retake her.
泰瑞最後的秘訣
Tyrell's final trick:
生育
Procreation.
更完美了  卻無法再生
Perfected, then lost.
但有個孩子
But there is a child.
把孩子帶來
Bring it to me.
是
Sir.
最出色的天使
The best angel of all.
對吧  露芙
Aren't you, Luv?
穿綠色夾克的男人
The man with the green jacket.
他殺了薩珀  查清楚他知道些什麼
The one who killed Sapper. Find out what he knows.
你好啊  帥哥
Hello, hello, A-Boy.
一個人嗎
You alone?
他是他媽的銀翼殺手
我認識他
這傢伙很危險，你跟我走嗎？
沒關係
It's fine.
願意給我買包煙嗎
Wanna buy a lady a cigarette?
你連笑都不笑
Oh, you don't even smile.
你沒聽到你朋友說的話嗎
Didn't you hear your friends?
你不知道我是誰嗎
Don't you know what I am?
知道
Yeah.
吃米飯的男人
Guy eating rice.
那是什麼
What's that?
是棵樹
It's a tree.
我從沒見過樹
Never seen a tree before.
很美
It's pretty.
已經死了
It's dead.
誰會留著一棵死樹呢
Now, who keeps a dead tree?
你不會殺了我吧  會嗎
You're not gonna kill me, are you?
不一定  你是什麼型號
Depends. What's your model number?
你看我眼睛下面不就知道了
Why don't you look under my eye and find out?
你不喜歡真正的女孩
You don't like real girls.
我一直在這兒
Well, I'm always here.
你不能拿
You can't take those.
當然  我通過正常程式  也有檔證明
Of course not. Proper channels and paperwork.
都在這兒
It's all here.
幫我拿一下
Hold this for me.
這呢  給你
Yep. Here you go.
珂珂死了
Coco is dead.
骨頭不見了
Bones are gone.
消息已經傳出去了  才用了多長時間
It's out. Already out. How long did that take?
有什麼消息  別告訴我什麼都沒有
So, what do you have for me? And don't say nothing.
我找到了那個
I found that.
一隻襪子
A sock?
-你從哪兒找到的  -薩珀家
- Where'd you find it? - Sapper's.
有其他東西嗎
Anything else?
我把剩下的都燒了
I burned everything else.
那這是什麼  這日期是什麼
Then what's this? What's that date?
是生日  還是死期
Is that a birthday? Is that a death day?
我還不知道
I don't know yet.
只有我意識到了會發生什麼嗎
Am I the only one that can see the fucking sunrise here?
這會毀掉世界的  K
This breaks the world, K.
我認識很多個複製人
You know, I've known a lot of your kind.
都很有用  但和你在一起  我有時會忘記
All useful, but with you, I sometimes forget.
我小時候  一個複製人都沒有
We didn't have any of you where I was a kid.
你記得什麼嗎
Do you remember anything?
關於以前的事你還記得多少
Before you were under me, you have any memories from before?
我有記憶
I have memories...
但都不是真實的  是植入的
but they're not real. They're just implants.
跟我說說
Tell me one.
你的童年記憶
From when you were a kid.
我覺得跟別人講童年的事很奇怪
I feel strange sharing a childhood story,
因為我沒有童年
considering I was never a child.
如果我命令你  你肯說嗎
Well, would it help you share if I told you it was an order?
我記得我以前有個玩具
I have one about a toy that I had.
一匹木頭小馬
A wooden horse.
底部刻了字
With an inscription underneath.
我只記得有一群小男孩想搶走它
All I remember is a group of boys trying to take it away from me.
所以我跑走了
So I run.
我想找個地方把它藏起來
I go looking for a place to hide it,
而我周圍只有一個黑黑的爐子
and the only place is this dark furnace.
那裡一片漆黑  我很害怕
It's very dark, and I'm very scared...
但那個木馬是我的全部  所以我還是進去了
but this horse is all I have, so I go in anyway.
然後  那些孩子抓住了我
Later on, those kids find me...
他們打我讓我告訴他們木馬在哪  但我沒說
and they beat me to tell them where it is, but I don't.
就這些
That's it.
小小K保護自己的東西
Little K, fighting for what's his.
這個故事不錯
It's a good one.
看著我
Look at me.
我們都在尋找真實
We're all just looking out for something real.
如果我全喝了會怎麼樣
What happens if I finish that?
我是不是該回去工作了  長官
Shouldn't I get back to work, madam?
再調查一下DNA庫
Check back in after DNA base.
DNA檔案室
洛杉磯警局
KD6-3.7警官
Officer KD6 - 3.7.
請求搜索
Request.
輸入日期
2021年6月10日出生的孩子的DNA記錄
DNA records children born 6-10-21.
查詢有無異常
Looking for anomalies.
錯 誤
有晶體備份資料嗎
You have the satcrystal backup?
所有注釋資料損壞
傳輸頭部不可用
錯 誤
無法繼續
好吧
Okay.
手動搜索吧
Run it raw.
人類就是由資料構成的
Mere data makes a man.
A  C  T  G
A and C and T and G.
你的基因編碼  只由四個字母組成
The alphabet of you. All from four symbols.
我只有兩個
I'm only two:
1和0
One and zero.
雖然只有一半  但卻加倍優雅  親愛的
Half as much but twice as elegant, sweetheart.
你不叫我長官嗎
You don't prefer your madam?
你剛剛在偷聽
You were listening.
也許
Maybe.
你沒有告訴她真相  看來你還不夠喜歡她
You didn't like her enough to tell her the truth.
2021年6月10日
Six, 10 and 21.
也沒什麼好說的
There's nothing to tell.
這故事你跟我講了多少遍了
How many times have you told me that story?
你的記憶
Your memory?
底部刻著的日期
The date carved beneath.
2021年6月10日
Six, 10 and 21.
巧合嗎
Coincidence?
一個危險的巧合
A dangerous coincidence.
我早就知道你很特別
I always knew you were special.
或許這就是你的特別之處
Maybe this is how.
一個孩子
A child.
自然出生
Of woman born.
通過生產降臨到這個世上
Pushed into the world.
被人需要
Wanted.
沐浴在愛中
Loved.
若這是真的
Well, if it were true...
我餘生都會被我這樣的人追殺
I'd be hunted for the rest of my life by someone just like me.
偶爾做下夢也沒什麼
It's okay to dream a little.
-不是嗎  -你是我  就不會這樣想了
- Isn't it? - Not if you're us.
停
Stop.
對比4847和2181組資料
Put up 4847 and 2181 side-by-side.
完全一致  翻譯
They're identical. Translate.
翻譯
數據
檔案編號
性別
女
男
數據組
存儲等級
一男一女
A boy and a girl.
-這不可能  -怎麼了
- It's impossible. - Why?
性別
男
數據組
性別
男
數據組
兩個人的DNA不可能完全相同
Two people can't have identical DNA.
性別
男
數據組
性別
男
數據組
女
性別
男
數據組
女
性別
男
數據組
性別
女
有一個人是假的  是複製品
One of these isn't real. It's a copy.
性別
數據組
女
性別
數據組
女
性別
數據組
翻譯
數據
檔案編號
性別
女
男
數據組
存儲等級
處理中心
翻譯
數據
檔案編號
處理中心
莫里科爾
驗證
他們都在莫瑞爾·科爾孤兒院呆過
They were both processed at the Morrill Cole Orphanage.
檔案編號
附加資訊
注釋
死亡證明書
莫瑞爾·科爾孤兒院
加拉太綜合征
這上面說女孩死在那了
It says the girl died there.
死因是遺傳缺陷
Genetic disorder.
迦拉太綜合症
Galatians Syndrome.
男孩
And the boy...
消失了
disappears.
那個孤兒院在哪
Where's the orphanage?
想出去兜風嗎
You wanna go for a ride?
正在離開
大洛杉磯地區
洛杉磯市政廢品處理
聖地牙哥區
到了
Well, here we are.
系上安全帶
Buckle up.
K
K?
K  K
K? K?
K  K  K
K? K? K?
退後
Stay back.
開火
Fire again.
Fire.
朝東六十米
Two hundred feet to the east.
開火
Fire.
北面
Go north.
開火
Fire.
停  向東轉20度
Stop. Twenty degrees east.
停
Stop.
放大
Zoom in.
再拉近一點
Closer.
拜託
Oh, come on.
站起來
Get up.
幹活去
Do your fucking job.
找到那個孩子
Find the child.
看好車
Watch the car.
每一塊都要找出來
Every last piece,
否則我就把你們趕到外面去
or I'll put you outside where the sky is raining...
任火球砸死你們
where it's raining fire!
你們是來幹活的
You're in here to work.
不幹活的人  我不需要
And if you're not working, I don't need you.
我不需要任何...
I don't need any of--
鎳用來建殖民飛船
The nickel is for the colonial ships.
這是他們或我們最接近...
Closest any of them or any of us is gonna get...
外星殖民地的美好生活的時候了
to that grand life Off-world.
我真的鼓勵他們玩耍  讓他們有事可做
And I encourage play, I do. Keeps them occupied...
還能保持身手敏捷  對吧
and it makes them nimble, right?
但是  是工作
But it's work.
是工作將他們塑造成有價值的孩子
It's work that molds them into a child worth having.
選吧
So come on, now.
你想要什麼類型的
What sort do you have in mind?
我這兒各種都有
Because I got all kinds.
-不不不  -我不買
- Oh, no, no, no. - I'm not buying.
不不  這只是我的生存手段  我也很公平
No, no, no. This is just my game, and I play it fair.
不不  比你大的人物...
No. No, I mean, bigger than you....
比你大的人物也曾讓我關閉這裡
Bigger than you have tried to shut me down. Bigger than you.
而且他們還是真實的人類
And they were men, at that.
約30年前  有個小男孩來過這裡
A little boy came through here about 30 years back.
我要看你的記錄
I need to see your records.
合法安置  私下買賣  我都要看
Legitimate placements, private sales, everything.
我沒保存那麼久以前的記錄
Don't keep records that far back.
-沒有嗎  -沒有
- You don't? - I don't.
抱歉
Sorry.
幫不了你
Can't help you.
-是嗎  -是的
- You can't? - Nope.
我覺得你幫得了
I think you can.
我覺得你這樣的人記性都很好
I think someone like you keeps a long memory.
告訴我你記得什麼
Now you can tell me what you remember...
否則我一槍打爆你的腦袋  親自看看裡面
or I can put a hole right here and take a look.
他們當時在笑  你說什麼來著  你說什麼了
They were laughing and what was it you said? What'd you say?
你來不來
Are you coming?
在哪裡
Where is it?
天啊
Oh, God.
哪裡  哪裡  哪裡
Where, where, where?
我找不到  這裡
I don't see it. Here.
不見了
It's gone.
一整年的記錄
It's the entire year.
不是我幹的
I didn't do that.
不是我
That wasn't me.
我沒撕掉  不是我
I didn't. Wasn't me.
我總是告訴你
I always told you.
你很特別
You're special.
自然出生
Born.
而非人造
Not made.
被小心地藏起來
Hidden with care.
現在是真正的男孩了
A real boy now.
真正的男孩需要一個真正的名字
A real boy needs a real name.
喬
Joe.
"喬"
"Joe"?
你太重要了  不能只叫K
You're too important for K.
你母親一定會為你取名的
Your mother would've named you.
喬
Joe.
-喬  -別說了
- Joe. - Stop.
我如何確定記憶是不是被植入的
How do I know if a memory is an implant or not?
記憶由誰製造
Who makes the memories?
安娜·斯特林博士
Dr. Ana Stelline?
有訪客
A visitor.
能談談嗎
Is that okay?
可以
Yes.
只是不常有訪客
It's just unusual.
幸會  KD6-3.7警官
Nice to meet you, Officer KD6 - 3.7.
抱歉  是個折中的免疫系統
Sorry. It's a compromised immune system.
只要待在玻璃後面  就有自由的生活
A life of freedom, so long as it's behind glass.
-所以你才沒去外星殖民地嗎  -是的
- Is that why you're not Off-world? - Yes.
我父母已經拿到通行證了  但我病了
My parents had our passes in pocket, but I took sick.
於是我過上了新的生活
So it was a new life for me.
他們把我關進籠子裡
And they put me in my cage...
在裡面放滿讓我快樂的事物
filled it with everything they could to keep me happy.
只除了陪伴  我以前從不缺乏陪伴
Except company, of course. And I was used to crowds.
有什麼能幫你的
What can I help you with?
你也許能幫我破一個案子
Thought you might be able to help me with a case.
已經很久沒人找我
Oh, that's the most interesting thing
幫這麼有趣的忙了
I've been offered to help with in ages.
我邊工作邊聽你說  行嗎
Do you mind if I work while you talk?
沒問題
Of course.
我保證會認真聽
I promise I hear every word.
聽說你是最出色的記憶製造者
They say you're the best memory-maker there is.
他們過譽了
Well, then, they're kind.
我很喜歡生日派對
I love birthday parties.
你為華萊士工作嗎
You work for Wallace?
是分包合同  我是他的供應商
Subcontract. I'm one of his suppliers.
他想把我買斷
He offered to buy me out,
但我把握自己所能得到的自由
but I take my freedom where I can find it.
你為什麼如此擅長
Why are you so good?
是什麼讓你的記憶如此真實
What makes your memories so authentic?
每個藝術家都會將自己融入作品中
Well, there's a bit of every artist in their work.
但我8歲時被關在一個無菌房間裡
But I was locked in a sterile chamber at 8...
如果我想看外面的世界  只能靠想像
so if I wanted to see the world, I had to imagine it.
我變得非常擅長想像
Got very good at imagining.
華萊士需要我的才能來維持穩定的產品
Wallace needs my talent to maintain a stable product.
我認為這是仁慈
I think it's only kind.
複製人的生活很艱難  被迫做人類不願做的事
Replicants live such hard lives, made to do what we'd rather not.
我無法幫助你們的未來
I can't help your future...
但我可以給你們美好的記憶  回想時也有快樂
but I can give you good memories to think back on and smile.
這挺好的
It's nice.
不止如此  這記憶很真實
It's better than nice. It feels authentic.
如果記憶是真實的
And if you have authentic memories,
就會有真實的人類反應
you have real human responses.
你說對不對
Wouldn't you agree?
記憶都是你造出來的  還是也會用真實的
Are they all constructed, or do you ever use ones that are real?
用真實記憶是違法的  警官
It's illegal to use real memories, officer.
你怎麼區分
How can you tell the difference?
你能看出來一件事
Can you tell if something...
真的發生過嗎
really happened?
人們一般以為細節多就是真的
They all think it's about more detail.
但記憶不是這樣的
But that's not how memory works.
我們憶起的是感覺
We recall with our feelings.
真實的應該是紛亂的
Anything real should be a mess.
我演示給你看
I can show you.
坐吧
Sit.
現在回想你想讓我看見的記憶
Now, think about the memory you want me to see.
不用太仔細  想像就好
Not even that hard. Just picture it.
讓它在腦海中播放
Let it play.
有人真正經歷過這段  沒錯
Someone lived this, yes.
這件事發生過
This happened.
我就知道是真的
I know it's real.
天殺的
Goddamn it!
KD6-3.7警官  長官命令你回警署
Officer KD6 - 3.7. Madam is calling you in.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
放下槍  手放在我能看見的地方
Drop your gun and keep your hands where I can see them.
-細胞  -細胞
- Cells. - Cells.
-你進過孤兒院嗎  細胞  -細胞
- Have you ever been in an institution? Cells. - Cells
如果你沒能盡責
When you're not performing your duties,
-他們會把你關進小房間嗎  細胞  -細胞
- do they keep you in a little box? Cells. - Cells.
-相連  -相連
- Interlinked. - Interlinked.
牽著你所愛之人的手是什麼感覺
What's it like to hold the hand of someone you love?
-相連  -相連
- Interlinked. - Interlinked.
-細胞之間相連  -細胞之間相連
- Within cells interlinked. - Within the cells interlinked.
-恐怖  -恐怖
- Dreadfully. - Dreadfully.
警官:
基線測試
偵測到異常
-充滿了恐怖是什麼感覺  恐怖  -恐怖
- What's it like to be filled with dread? Dreadfully. - Dreadfully.
-你喜歡跟其他人隔開嗎  單獨  -單獨
- Do you like being separated from other people? Distinct. - Distinct.
-單獨得恐怖  黑暗  -單獨得恐怖  黑暗
- Dreadfully distinct. Dark. - Dreadfully distinct. Dark.
-細胞之間相連  -細胞之間相連
- Within cells interlinked. - Within the cells interlinked.
-與那主幹再相連  -與那主幹再相連
- Within one stem. - Within one stem.
-單獨得恐怖  -單獨得恐怖
- And dreadfully distinct. - And dreadfully distinct.
-在那黑暗襯托下  -在那黑暗襯托下
- Against the dark. - Against the dark.
一座噴泉向上高噴的白水柱
A tall white fountain played.
你大幅偏離基準線
You're not even close to baseline.
都出去  關門
Out! And close the door.
你到底怎麼了
What the fuck is with you?
我讓你去辦案
I put you on a case.
特意強調過這案子有多重要
I impressed on you the importance of that case...
結果我們卻發現  你在升級中心外面亂晃
and then we pick you up fucking around outside an upgrade center?
掃描顯示  你內心像變了個人
Scan said you didn't look like you on the inside.
離基準線差得太遠
Miles off your baseline.
-你知道這意味著什麼嗎  -我找到那孩子了
- Do you know what that means? - I found the kid.
人們安排他做標準複製人的工作  做公務員
He was set up like a standard Replicant, put on a service job.
連他都不知道自己的身份
Even he didn't know who he was.
-然後呢  -已經做完了
- And? - And it's done.
-"做完了"是什麼意思  -按你命令做的
- What does that mean, "It's done"? - What you asked.
完成了
It's done.
操
Fuck.
你剛剛阻止了一枚炸彈爆炸
You just stopped a bomb from going off.
幹得好
You did good.
我可以讓你活著走出警察局
I can help you get out of this station alive...
給你48小時恢復正常狀態
but you have 48 hours to get back on track.
交出警徽和槍
Surrender your gun and badge.
下次基準線測試可就不是我負責了
And your next baseline test is out of my hands.
謝謝  長官
Thank you, madam.
你說得對
You were right.
一切都被你說中了
You were right about everything.
我還以為你不感興趣呢  工作狂
Thought you weren't interested, worky man.
你喜歡她  我看得出來
You liked her. I could tell.
沒關係
It's okay.
她是真的
She's real.
我想為你變真
I wanna be real for you.
對我來說你就是真的
You are real for me.
你家有位特別的姑娘
You have a special lady here.
好
Okay.
來吧
Let's do it.
看看你
Look at you.
安靜  我要同步
Quiet now, I have to sync.
喬伊會變成任何你想要的人
Joi is anything you want her to be.
喬伊會去任何你想讓她去的地方
Joi goes anywhere you want her to go.
99.9%消毒水
99.9 percent detoxified water.
是樹做的
It's from a tree.
結束了
I'm done with you.
你可以走了
You can go now.
安靜
Quiet now.
我當過你
I've been inside you.
你沒什麼了不起的
Not so much there as you think.
喝咖啡嗎
Coffee?
他們很快就會來抓我
They'll be coming after me soon.
我和你一起走
I'm coming with you.
但不能這樣
But not like this.
要是他們來這找你
If they come here looking for you,
他們會讀取我所有的記憶
they'll have access to all my memories.
你得把我從主控臺上刪掉
You have to delete me from the console.
我的禮物
My present.
把我放進去
Put me there.
不行
I can't do that.
想想看
Think about it:
要是它出了閃失  就全完了
If anything happens to this, that's it.
你就不復存在了
You're gone.
對
Yes.
就像真人一樣
Like a real girl.
求你了
Please.
喬  求你了
Joe, please.
我想這樣做
I want this.
但我自己做不來
But I can't do it myself.
毀掉天線
Break the antenna.
真木頭，你真有錢，朋友
我可以給你一匹真馬
你要真馬嗎？
我不要一匹真馬
I don't need a real horse.
不，我可以給你弄一匹，就像華萊士的東西
我不要真馬  只想知道它是從哪來的
I don't need a real horse. I just wanna find out where it's from.
聞起來像舊塵土
但是這個木頭結構是新的
核反應爐的輻射
Radiation from a reactor?
不，更不穩定
氚
很老，很老
符合髒彈輻射值
It matches a dirty bomb.
只有一個地方曾經有過這麼強烈的輻射
只有一個地方經受過這麼強的轟炸
There's only one place that dirty.
那兒沒人生活
Nobody lives there.
你剛才問我這是哪裡來的
現在我告訴你了
那麼你想要什麼？
一匹馬？一頭羊？
外星殖民地的手續
你想要什麼，巴德吉博士都能給你搞來
五倍
Go to five.
四倍  往左30度
Four, 30 degrees to the left.
鏡頭上搖
Tilt up.
升高到122米
Elevate to 400 feet.
輻射分析
Radiation analysis.
輻射水準：
普    通
往前
Move forward.
鏡頭上搖
Tilt up.
停
Stop.
往前
Move forward.
五倍
Go to five.
七倍  往前
Seven, move forward.
六倍
Six.
停
Stop.
七倍
Go to seven.
八倍
Eight.
九倍
Nine.
熱感分析
Heat analysis.
生命
Life.
這是什麼
What is it?
猜猜會有什麼發現
Guess we're about to find out.
太黑了
Too dark in here.
我喜歡他
I like him.
他是個好孩子
He's a good boy.
他在哪
Where is he?
我不知道  他不執勤
I have no idea. He's off-duty.
四處找找吧
Check around.
我找過了
I checked...
好孩子會去的地方都找過了
...anywhere a good boy might go.
你來晚了
You're too late.
已經消失了
It's gone.
他銷毀了
He destroyed it.
一切都銷毀了
Everything about it.
除了你已經拿走的那箱骨頭
Well, except for the box of bones that you already took.
我打賭  那箱骨頭還不夠  所以你來了
Which, I'll wager, wasn't enough. Here you are.
你個小東西
You tiny thing.
面對那麼不可思議的新事物  你卻只想扼殺掉
In the face of the fabulous new, your only thought is to kill it?
害怕大變革
For fear of great change?
別妄想螳臂當車
You can't hold the tide with a broom.
不過我成功了
Except that I did.
他在哪
Where is he?!
你這麼肯定
You're so sure.
因為他親口告訴你
Because he told you.
因為我們永不撒謊
Because we never lie.
我會跟華萊氏先生說  是你先想開槍打我的
I'm gonna tell Mr. Wallace you tried to shoot me first.
我不得不殺了你
So I had to kill you.
那就動手吧
Then do what you gotta do.
長官
Madam.
KD6-3.7警官
Officer KD6 - 3.7.
你該不會恰好帶著一塊乳酪吧
Mightn't happen to have a piece of cheese about you, now?
你有嗎  孩子
Would you, boy?
《金銀島》
Treasure Island?
你看書
He reads.
很好
That's good.
我也看
Me too.
在這兒夜裡也沒什麼別的可做
Not much else to do around here at night anymore.
我總是夢見乳酪
Many is the night I dream of cheese...
大多數時候是烤過的
toasted, mostly.
你來幹什麼
What are you doing here?
我聽見了鋼琴聲
I heard the piano.
別撒謊
Don't lie.
撒謊很無禮
It's rude.
你是員警
You're a cop.
-我不是來抓你的  -是嗎
- I'm not here to take you in. - Oh, yeah?
那是幹什麼
Then, what?
我想問幾個問題
I just have some questions.
什麼問題
What questions?
待在這
Stay.
我不想傷害你
Look, I don't wanna hurt you.
但你逼我
But you're not making it easy.
我喜歡這首歌
I like this song.
我們可以一直打下去  或者去喝一杯
We could keep at this, or we could get a drink.
我選喝一杯
I'll take the drink.
這裡真氣派
This is really something.
整座城都曾經很氣派
The whole town was something.
曾經
One time.
忘掉煩惱
Forget your troubles...
看場演出
...see a show...
賭幾把
...gamble a little.
贏幾個錢輸幾個錢
Win some money, lose some money.
他們把錢弄得像糖一樣
They made money seem like candy.
你喜歡威士卡嗎
You like whiskey?
我這裡有幾百萬瓶
I've got millions...
威士卡
...of bottles of whiskey.
給
Here.
流血了
Bleeding.
它是真的嗎
Is it real?
我不知道
I don't know.
你問他
Ask him.
你有名字嗎
You got a name?
KD6-3.7警官
Officer KD6 - 3.7--
這不是名字  是序號
That's not a name. That's a serial number.
好吧
All right.
喬
Joe.
你想幹什麼  喬
What do you want, Joe?
-我想問你幾個問題  -比如
- I wanna ask you some questions. - Like what?
她叫什麼  你孩子的母親
Like what was her name, the mother of your child?
她什麼樣
What was she like?
-你們一起住嗎  -你問太多了
- You two live here together? - Too many questions.
我也幹過你的工作  做得很好
I had your job. I was good at it.
-那時候更簡單  -你為什麼要把它複雜化
- It was simpler then. - Why you making it complicated?
-你為什麼不回答問題  -什麼問題
- Why don't you answer the question? - What question?
我沒想到你這麼難辦
I didn't figure you as one for bullshit.
她叫什麼
What's her name?
瑞秋
Rachael.
她叫瑞秋
Her name was Rachael.
孩子後來怎麼了
What happened to the kid?
誰把他送到孤兒院  是你嗎
Who put it in the orphanage? Was it you?
我當時早就走了
I was long gone by then.
你沒見過你的親生孩子
You didn't even meet your own kid?
為什麼
Why?
計畫就是這樣的
Because that was the plan.
我教他們如何擾亂記錄  掩蓋蹤跡
I showed them how to scramble the records, cover their tracks.
每人都有分工  我的任務是離開
Everyone had a part. Mine was to leave.
然後是大斷電  抹掉了一切
Then the Blackout came, paved over everything.
就算我努力找了  也找不到那個孩子
Couldn't have found the child if I tried.
-你想找嗎  -不想
- Did you want to? - Not really.
-為什麼  -因為我們被人追捕
- Why not? - Because we were being hunted.
我不想讓人找到我們的孩子
I didn't want our child found...
被切開  被解剖
taken apart, dissected.
有時  愛一個人
Sometimes, to love someone...
就要變成陌生人
you gotta be a stranger.
敬陌生人
To strangers.
你做了什麼
What'd you do?
你把誰帶來了
Who'd you bring?
-我沒有  -是嗎
- No one. - Oh, yeah?
目標鎖定
Target locked.
他們知道你在這
They know you're here.
我一個人來的
I came alone.
真不乖
Bad dog.
停
Stop.
希望你對我們的產品滿意
I do hope you're satisfied with our product.
我愛
I love--
有個人想見你
Hey, there's someone who wants to meet you.
你可以相信我們
You can trust us.
你肯定想讓我往左上看
You must want me to look up and to the left.
她是福瑞莎
This is Freysa.
她和薩珀同在卡蘭星戰鬥過
She fought with Sapper on Calantha.
我認得你
I recognize you.
你幫他把孩子藏起來了
Did you help him hide the child?
我當時在場
I was there.
看見奇跡降生
I saw a miracle delivered.
一張完美的小臉朝我啼哭
A perfect little face crying up at me.
哭聲震天響
Mad as thunder.
你跟她在一起嗎
Were you with her?
瑞秋
Rachael?
她死在我懷裡
I held her as she died.
我們把孩子藏好  發誓保守秘密
We hid the child and made a vow to keep our secret.
所以薩珀甘願被你殺
That's why Sapper let you kill him.
我知道  孩子意味著我們不止奴隸
I knew that baby meant we are more than just slaves.
要是我們可以生孩子
If a baby can come from one of us...
意味著我們可以自己做主
we are our own masters.
比人類更人類
More human than humans.
革命馬上就要發生
A revolution is coming.
我們正在組建軍隊
And we're building an army.
我想解放同類
I want to free our people.
要是你想自由
If you want to be free...
加入我們
join us.
戴克  薩珀  你  我...
Deckard, Sapper, you, me...
跟即將到來的風暴相比  我們的命不值一提
our lives mean nothing next to a storm that's coming.
為正確的事業犧牲  這是我們能做的最有人性的事
Dying for the right cause is the most human thing we can do.
你帶華萊士找到了戴克
You led Wallace to Deckard.
不能讓戴克把華萊士引到我這兒
You cannot allow Deckard to lead Wallace to me.
你必須殺了戴克
You must kill Deckard.
戴克只想讓他的孩子平安
Deckard only wanted his baby to be safe.
他女兒很平安
And she is.
等時機來臨  我會讓全世界看到她...
When the time comes, I will show her to the world...
讓她帶領我們的軍隊
and she will lead our army.
女兒
"She"?
是啊
Of course.
瑞秋生了個女兒
Rachael had a daughter.
我親眼看著她降生
With my own eyes, I saw her come.
她臨走時  我給她穿上了藍色衣服
I dressed her in blue when it was time for her to go.
你藏的是個男孩
It was a boy that you hid.
只是大計畫的一部分而已
That is just a piece of the puzzle.
你以為是你
You imagined it was you?
你真這麼想
You did.
真的
我們都希望那孩子是自己
We all wish it was us.
所以我們才堅信
That's why we believe.
有人真正經歷過這段  沒錯
Someone lived this, yes.
我教他們如何擾亂記錄  掩蓋蹤跡
I showed them how to scramble the records, cover their tracks.
處理中心
莫里科爾孤兒院
狀態
死  亡
我親眼看著她降生
With my own eyes, I saw her come.
她臨走時  我給她穿上了藍色衣服
I dressed her in blue when it was time for her to go.
每個藝術家都會將自己融入作品中
There's a bit of every artist in their work.
那個總是跳出來
Always jumping, that one.
從沒想過要是落不回水裡怎麼辦
Never a thought of what to do if it made land.
世上所有勇氣都無法改變事實
All the courage in the world cannot alter fact.
我想見你已經非常久了
I have wanted to meet you for so very long.
我覺得你是個奇跡  戴克先生
You are a wonder to me, Mr. Deckard.
我有鎖
I had the lock.
也找到了鑰匙
I found the key.
但插入鎖孔的部分對不上  門還是打不開
Yet the pins do not align. The door remains locked.
我需要  戴克先生
I need the specimen to reach it, Mr. Deckard.
那孩子
The child.
我需要那孩子
I need the child.
教會所有人飛翔
To teach them all to fly.
上帝顧念瑞秋
And God remembered Rachel...
啟發了她的子宮
heeded her and opened her womb.
你喜歡我們的貓頭鷹嗎
Do you like our owl?
泰瑞爾檔案
音訊檔
2019年11月20日
是人造的嗎
It's artificial?
當然
Of course it is.
肯定很貴
Must be expensive.
極其昂貴  我叫瑞秋
Very. I'm Rachael.
泰瑞爾檔案
音訊檔
2019年11月20日
戴克
Deckard.
相同嗎
Is it the same...
現在和當時
...now, as then...
你和她初遇的時候
...the moment you met her?
這麼多年你一直回憶當時
All these years you looked back on that day...
沉醉于那段記憶的美好
drunk on the memory of its perfection.
她閃亮的唇
How shiny her lips.
你們立即相通相連
How instant your connection.
你就沒想過
Did it never occur to you
最初你們相遇就是為了這個
that's why you were summoned in the first place?
設計的目的就是
Designed to do nothing short of fall
那時那地為她出現
for her right then and there.
一切都是為了那個完美的標本
All to make that single perfect specimen.
假設你是被設計製造出來的話
That is, if you were designed.
是愛情
Love...
還是精確的數學推算
or mathematical precision.
沒錯
Yes.
不
No.
我知道真實是什麼
I know what's real.
讓自己一無所知  這招很聰明
It was very clever to keep yourself empty of information...
但這樣做讓你失去了一切
and all it cost you was everything.
但你依然能幫我
But you can still help me.
藏孩子  你也出力了
You had help in the hiding.
他們去哪了
Where did they go?
你肯定知道些什麼
I know you know something.
幫幫我
Help me...
我會極其慷慨地報答你
and very, very good things can come to you.
你沒有孩子
You don't have children...
是吧
do you?
我有上百萬個
Oh, I have millions.
你以為我只能用痛苦威脅你
You think I have nothing to offer but pain.
只不過我知道
Only I know...
你喜歡痛苦
you love pain.
痛苦時刻提醒著你  之前的快樂是真實的
Pain reminds you the joy you felt was real.
那就再來點快樂
More joy, then.
別害怕
Do not be afraid.
天使
An angel...
再造的
made again.
特別為你打造
For you.
你想我嗎
Did you miss me?
你不愛我嗎
Don't you love me?
她眼睛是綠色的
Her eyes were green.
外星殖民地
Off-world...
我有讓你開口所需的一切
I have everything I need to make you talk.
你還不知道什麼是痛苦
You do not know what pain is yet.
你會知道的
You will learn.
你好  帥哥
Hello, handsome.
今天可夠嗆了吧
What a day.
你好像很寂寞
You look lonely.
我可以幫你驅散寂寞
I can fix that.
你這個喬看起來不錯
You look like a good joe.
嬌
伊
如你所聞
所見
為正確的事業犧牲  這是我們能做的最有人性的事
Dying for the right cause is the most human thing we can do.
是因為你們從未見過奇跡
Because you've never seen a miracle.
你正在進入洛杉磯機場禁飛區
You're entering Los Angeles Airport restricted airspace.
確認身份
Confirm your identity.
S144XD運輸機  確認
Transport S-14-4-XD. Confirmed.
我是06
Space, this is 0-6.
飛往太空  路線030
Outbound departure, route 0-3-0.
我們要去哪
Where are we going?
回家
Home.
二號駕駛員陣亡
Drive two down.
啟用備用計畫
Backup engaged.
警告
Warning.
-能行嗎  -太低了
- Can we make it? - We're too low!
調頭回去
Take us back!
拉升高度
Get us up.
打開門
Open the door.
我是最出色的
I'm the best one.
外星殖民地等著我們呢
Off-world is waiting.
喬  喬
Joe. Joe!
喬
Joe!
你就應該讓我死在那
You should have let me die out there.
你已經死了
You did.
你淹死了
You drowned out there.
現在你可以見你女兒了
You're free to meet your daughter now.
斯黛琳
最好的記憶都是她的
All the best memories are hers.
為什麼
Why?
為什麼這樣對我
Who am I to you?
去見你女兒吧
Go meet your daughter.
你沒事吧
You okay?
稍等一下
Just a moment.
好美啊
Beautiful, isn't it?
導演
鄧尼斯·維倫紐瓦
編劇
漢普頓·範徹 和 邁克爾·格林
故事
漢普頓·範徹
美國艾肯傳媒集團  出品
聯合出品
美國哥倫比亞電影公司
英國雷德利·斯科特工作室  製作
美國艾肯娛樂公司  製作
美國巴德·約金工作室  製作
聯合制作
美國托裡登影片公司 和 美國16:14娛樂公司
鄧尼斯·維倫紐瓦  電影作品
瑞恩·高斯林
哈里森·福特
銀翼殺手
改編自 菲力浦·K·迪克 小說
《仿生人會夢見電子羊嗎？》
製片人
安德魯·A·科索夫 & 布羅德里克·詹森
巴德·約金 & 辛西婭·塞克斯·約金
執行製片
雷德利·斯科特
比爾·卡拉羅
執行製片
蒂姆·甘博
弗蘭克·吉斯特拉
執行製片
耶魯·巴迪克
瓦爾·希爾
聯合執行製片
伊恩·邁克葛羅音
阿沙·格林伯格
聯合制片
卡爾·O·羅傑斯
達納·貝爾卡斯楚
史蒂文·P·瓦格納
攝影指導
羅傑·狄金斯
藝術指導
鄧尼斯·蓋斯納
剪輯
喬·沃克
視覺特效
約翰·尼爾森
服裝設計
蕾妮·愛普勒
配樂
本傑明·沃菲斯齊
漢斯·季默
里安娜·德·阿瑪斯
西爾維婭·侯克斯
羅賓·萊特
麥肯茲·大衛斯
卡拉·朱裡
連尼·詹姆斯
肖恩·楊
愛德華·詹姆斯·奧莫斯
戴夫·巴蒂斯塔
傑瑞德·萊托
巴哈德·阿布迪
西婭姆·阿巴斯
伍德·哈裡斯
大衛·達斯馬齊連
選角導演
芙蘭辛·梅斯勒
音樂監督
戴瓦·安德森
音效剪輯
馬克·曼吉尼
音效設計
席奧·格林